<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dept APP</string>
    <string name="open_drawer">Open Drawer</string>
    <string name="close_drawer">Close Drawer</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="schedule">Schedule</string>
    <string name="demoText">Minutes of the 141th Academic Council Meeting, Chief Guest Mr Lakhan Sir.</string>
    <string name="demoDate">17/01/2023</string>
    <string name="collegeAdd">Since 1996\nICARE Complex, Hatiberia Haldia, Dist-Purba Medinipore, WB, Pin-721657 (+913224)252900/255166</string>
    <string name="ACMDescription">The Association for Computing Machinery (ACM) is the world’s largest educational and scientific society uniting professionals, educators and researchers in the field of computer science to inspire dialogue, share resources and address the challenges in the domain. The purpose of this organization is to advance the scientific development, construction and application of the new machinery for computing, reasoning, and handling of information. The mission is to offer the students an opportunity to learn, innovate and grow into intellectuals, visionaries and technocrats, who contribute to promoting the advancements in science and technology. The ACM India Council is an effort of ACM aimed at improving the level of ACM activities across the country.</string>
    <string name="PlacementDescription">HIT has been consistently setting records of campus placements amongst private institutions in India. Producing graduates and postgraduates who are well equipped to handle the working norms of the Industry and Commerce in the public and the private sectors has been the primary aim of the Institute. It makes significant efforts to ensure enhanced employability through rigorous professional trainings at reputed industries and corporate houses. A series of in-house grooming programs e.g. interactive seminars and workshops, personality development classes, in depth counselling by experts, mock interviews and tutorials conducted by some of our finest faculties to enhance our students’ chances in a competitive job market.</string>
    <string name="dept_desc">The department of Information Technology has been offering undergraduate course in IT since 2000. At present the current intake of the department is 180 with the addition of 5% TFW and 20% Lateral entrant. Within a very short span of time, the department has created an excellent learning environment with dedicated young faculty members, technical staff, excellent laboratories and innovative academic processes. In order to perform the complex functions the modern Information Technology would use high configured computers along with the various software such as Linux, Database management systems, Adobe, Visual Studio, Sound forge, Anaconda etc. The department provides computational facilities for system level programmers, application development and research. For application level developers, complete enterprise level suites such as Machine Learning, Data Science, Multimedia, Web Technology etc. The department provides good training and placement opportunities to all its students. The Department of IT got the NBA accreditation on the year of 2020 for three years of span. The Department of Information Technology is imparting technical Education of high quality to the aspiring youth of the country. The department with the passage of its evolution and growth has succeeded in creating its place of excellence within the Institute as well as among its counterparts in the country. It has been attracting bright students from all parts of the country for quality education in Information Technology at Under Graduate level. During the course of time it has offered opportunities to its inmates in the area of quality education. The mission behind the Department of Information Technology is to impart high quality education and spawn eminent graduates to carry out leading-edge research in the discipline of Information Technology. The department has qualified and experienced faculty in the areas of Computer Architecture, Database Systems, Image Processing, Artificial Intelligence, Data Mining, machine Learning, Wireless Networks, Computer Networks, and Software Engineering, etc.</string>
</resources>